Inventory of the Constantine Peter Arnold papers, 1841-1943
University of Wyoming. American Heritage Center.
- Series VI. Legal Files
  - Interest on Herrick Loan Default, undated (Box 24)
  - Judgments (5), undated (Box 25)
  - Last Will of Hannah C. Arnold, undated (Box 25)
  - Leases (5), undated (Box 25)
  - Legal Notice, undated (Box 25)
  - Letter of Credit, undated (Box 25)
  - Location Notice, undated (Box 25)
  - Marshaling Assets (3), undated (Box 25)
  - Meetings - Laramie Valley National Farm Loan Association, undated (Box 25)
  - Meetings - McDonald Live Stock Co. (4), undated (Box 25)
  - Meetings - Millbrook Land and Live Stock Co. (11), undated (Box 25)
  - Meetings - Red-Butte Land and Live Stock Co., undated (Box 25)
  - Meetings - Tolec Live Stock Co., undated (Box 25)
  - Memorandum (3), undated (Box 25)
  - Memorandum Brief of Plaintiffs on Motion to Make Petition Definite and Certain, undated (Box 25)
  - Memorandum Brief of Relator on Demurrer to Petition, undated (Box 25)
  - Memorandum for the Assistant Attorney General (4), undated (Box 25)
  - Memorandum on Redemption, undated (Box 25)
  - Memorandum Submitted in Preparation of Judgment in Laramie Valley Municipal Irrigation District. Case (2), undated (Box 25)
  - Minutes of Meeting - Laramie Valley N.F.L.A., undated (Box 25)
  - Miscellaneous Legal Documents, undated (Box 25)
  - Mortgage Deeds (17), undated (Box 25)
  - Motion and Affidavit, undated (Box 25)
  - Motion to Make Petition More Definite and Certain, undated (Box 25)
  - Motion to Objection, undated (Box 25)
  - Notes (2), undated (Box 25)
  - Notice (2), undated (Box 25)
  - Notice Location or Placer Mining Claim, undated (Box 25)
  - Notice of Amendment of Location, undated (Box 25)
  - Notice of Dissolution of the Rock River State Bank (2), undated (Box 25)
  - Notice of Foreclosure (5), undated (Box 25)
  - Notice of Intended Taking and Decree of Condemnation (3), undated (Box 25)
  - Notice of Presentation of Petition to Organize an Irrigation District (2), undated (Box 25)
  - Notice of Sale in Partition, undated (Box 25)
  - Notice of Take Depositions (3), undated (Box 25)
  - Notice to Appropriator, undated (Box 25)
  - Nurses’ Certificate, undated (Box 25)
  - Oath of Commissioners, undated (Box 26)
  - Order (12), undated (Box 26)
  - Order Appointing Commissioners for Partition, undated (Box 26)
  - Order Approving Report, undated (Box 26)
  - Order Denying Motion to Make Petition Definite and Certain, undated (Box 26)
  - Order Disposing of Demurrers to Petition, undated (Box 26)
  - Order for Sale of Premises where Partition Cannot Be Made (3), undated (Box 26)
  - Order Granting Additional Time, undated (Box 26)
  - Order of Business of the Stockholders Meeting, undated (Box 26)
  - Order of Court (2), undated (Box 26)
  - Order of Distribution, undated (Box 26)
  - Order of Publication, undated (Box 26)
  - Order Permitting Intervention, undated (Box 26)
  - Order to Enter Upon and Appropriate to Land, undated (Box 26)
  - Organization meeting (3), undated (Box 26)
  - Outline of Findings of court, undated (Box 26)
  - Patent for State Lands (2), undated (Box 26)
  - Petition and Report, undated (Box 26)
  - Petition for Foreclosure, undated (Box 26)
  - Petition for Lease of State or School Lands, undated (Box 26)
  - Petition of the Rock Mountain Gas Co. for Leave to Intervene, undated (Box 26)
  - Petitions, undated (Box 26)
  - Physical Examination, undated (Box 26)
  - Plea of Axel L. Palmer (3), undated (Box 26)
  - Policy Loan Agreement, undated (Box 26)
  - Power of Attorney, undated (Box 26)
  - Praecipe, undated (Box 26)
  - Quit Claim Deeds (12), undated (Box 26)
  - Receipts (4), undated (Box 26)
  - Record of Proceedings, undated (Box 26)
  - Release of Mortgage, undated (Box 26)
  - Releases (5), undated (Box 26)
  - Releases of Chattel Mortgage (4), undated (Box 26)
  - Reply, undated (Box 26)
  - Reply Brief of Clara Bell, undated (Box 26)
  - Report, undated (Box 26)
  - Report (Economic Warfare Unit Report), undated (Box 26)
  - Report of Sale, undated (Box 26)
  - Report of Secretary-Treasurer of Laramie Valley, undated (Box 26)
  - Report of Sheriff on Sale, undated (Box 26)
  - Report on the Survey of the Lone Tree Reservoir, undated (Box 26)
  - Resolution (3), undated (Box 26)
  - Sheriff's Deed of Foreclosure, undated (Box 27)
  - Sheriff’s Deed (4), undated (Box 27)
  - Special Meeting - Laramie Valley N.F.L.A. (2), undated (Box 27)
  - Special Warranty Deed, undated (Box 27)
  - Statement of Account of the Millbrook L. & L S. Co., undated (Box 27)
  - Statement of C.P. Arnold - Re: Estate of Robert Gardner (3), undated (Box 27)
  - Statement of Mortgage Indebtedness, undated (Box 27)
  - Statement of Mr. Sevison, Engineer, undated (Box 27)
  - Stipulation (3), undated (Box 27)
  - Stipulation of Settlement and Dismissal, undated (Box 27)
  - Summons, undated (Box 27)
  - Supplemental Agreement, undated (Box 27)
  - Synopsis of Original Petition FLB Case, undated (Box 27)
  - Testimony - Re: Hunter vs. Sowder, undated (Box 27)
  - Transcript Judgment Docket “C” District Court, undated (Box 27)
  - Transcript of Exceptions, undated (Box 27)
  - Transcript of Proceedings, undated (Box 27)
  - Translation, undated (Box 27)
  - Trust Deeds (2), undated (Box 27)
  - Warranty Deed (18), undated (Box 27)
  - Writ of Partition, undated (Box 27)
- Series VII. Miscellaneous Printed Materials and Photographs
  - 10-mark German banknote, 1920 (Box 45)
  - 100-mark German banknote, 1920 (Box 45)
  - Athletics of the Mind, a Commencement Address, undated (Box 45)
  - Biographies of Composers: Mozart, Haydn, Strauss, Bizet, Tchaikovsky, Ravel, undated (Box 45)
  - The Bliss of Ignorance, a Commencement Address, undated (Box 45)
  - The Coroner’s Jury, undated (Box 45)
  - Invitations to Winter Picnics (30), 1923-1925 (Box 45)
  - Key Trends in Finnish Literature, undated (Box 45)
  - Magazine - Wyoming Pioneer Association, 1929, Contains an Article on Joe Rankin’s Record Run, undated (Box 34)
  - Natural Bridge - Converse County, undated (Box 31)
  - Newspaper Clippings, undated (Box 38)
  - Note - Nature Notes from Yellowstone National Park, Vol. 26, No. 3, 1952 May-June (Box 39)
  - Notes (Variety of Material), undated (Box 37)
  - Photographs - Laramie river (1), undated (Box 45)
  - Photographs - Snowy Range (19), undated (Box 45)
  - Photographs - Yukon River (29), undated (Box 45)
  - Photos (13), undated (Box 40)
  - Plants of Rocky Mountain National Park, Ruth A. Nelson, undated (Box 45)
  - The Present-Day Theatre in Finland, Ester-Margret von Frenckell, undated (Box 45)
  - Scrapbook of Cartoons, undated (Box 45)
  - Sheet Music - Dreamland, undated (Box 45)
  - Some Characteristics of Finnish Literature, Irma Rantavaara, undated (Box 45)
  - Songs of Bethlehem, Elizabeth Arnold Stone, undated (Box 45)
  - A Survey of Finnish Music, Anne-Marie Beaurain, undated (Box 45)
  - The Vanished Frontier, a collection of Essays, undated (Box 45)
  - Maps
    - Alabama, undated (Box 36)
    - Albany County, Wyoming, undated (Box 36)
    - Arizona, undated (Box 36)
    - Arkansas, undated (Box 36)
    - Colorado (2), undated (Box 36)
    - Hutton Reservoir Laramie, Wyoming (Blueprint), undated (Box 36)
    - Idaho, undated (Box 36)
    - Illinois, undated (Box 36)
    - Indiana, undated (Box 36)
    - Kansas, undated (Box 36)
    - Kentucky, undated (Box 36)
    - Laramie Rivers, undated (Box 36)
    - Laramie, Wyoming (Blueprint), undated (Box 36)
    - Missouri, undated (Box 36)
    - Montana (4), undated (Box 36)
    - New Jersey, undated (Box 36)
    - New York (2), undated (Box 36)
    - North Carolina, undated (Box 36)
    - North Dakota, undated (Box 36)
    - Ohio-Michigan, undated (Box 36)
    - Porto Rican, undated (Box 36)
    - Shoshone Indian National Forest, undated (Box 36)
    - South Carolina, undated (Box 36)
    - South Carolina, undated (Box 36)
    - Texas, undated (Box 36)
    - Township Maps, undated (Box 36)
    - Virginia (2), undated (Box 36)
    - Washington, undated (Box 36)
    - Wyoming (2), undated (Box 36)
    - Wyoming (2) (Blueprint), undated (Box 36)
    - Wyoming-Montana, undated (Box 36)
  - Pamphlets
    - Alden’s Juvenile Gem, undated (Box 39)
    - Banquet Tendered to Members of the Wyoming Bar, undated (Box 39)
    - The Bliss of Ignorance (5), undated (Box 39)
    - Can the Courts Aid Cooperative Marketing? (4), undated (Box 39)
    - Coal-Land Laws, undated (Box 39)
    - The Coroner’s Jury (5), undated (Box 39)
    - Court of Appeals (3), undated (Box 39)
    - The Decisions Relating to the Public Lands, undated (Box 39)
    - Easter services (3), undated (Box 39)
    - Field Entrenchments, undated (Box 39)
    - The Geographical Review, undated (Box 39)
    - Geology and Coal and Oil Resources of the Hanna and Carbon Basins, undated (Box 39)
    - Geology of Freezeout Mountain-Bald Mountain Area, Carbon County, Wyoming, undated (Box 39)
    - In the Supreme Court of the State of Wyoming, undated (Box 39)
    - Invitation to Winter Picnic, undated (Box 39)
    - Kansas Reprints III, undated (Box 39)
    - Laws Administered by the Farm Credit Administration, undated (Box 39)
    - The March of Human Life (2), undated (Box 39)
    - Medicine Bow National Forest, undated (Box 39)
    - Merrie Christmas 1921 (3), undated (Box 39)
    - Official Register of Princeton University, undated (Box 39)
    - Princeton University 164th Annual Commencement, undated (Box 39)
    - Record, Case No. 14,384, undated (Box 39)
    - Regulations Concerning Coal Mining Leases, Permits and Licenses, undated (Box 39)
    - Roma, undated (Box 39)
    - Selections from the Story of Plant Migration Revealed by Fossils, undated (Box 39)
    - The Supreme Court (2), undated (Box 39)
    - United States Mining Laws, undated (Box 39)
    - The Vanished Frontier (4), undated (Box 39)
    - Winter Birthday Picnic, undated (Box 39)
    - Wyoming Pioneer Association (4), undated (Box 39)